# **ELDO VARGHESE PAUL**

Anita Villa, Near Railway Station

R.S.P.O Thiruvalla

Mob: 8943233639 Email: eldopaul04@gmail.com



#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Looking forward to an opportunity in the field of sales & marketing to utilize my personal and professional qualities in a multi-national organization which gives me opportunities to demonstrate my competency and allow me a steadily paced rate of professional growth and development. Innovative Sales Executive with extensive knowledge of product sales and best-in-class services. Expert negotiator with proven success increasing profits and optimizing revenue streams.

### WORK HISTORY

### > NIPPON MOTOR CORPORATION PVT LTD

SALES EXECUTIVE

**OCTOBER 2017 - MAY 2019** 

### **Key Responsibilities:**

- 1. Sales of premium Toyota vehicles including: Innova Crysta, Fortuner, Corolla Altis, Camry, Land Cruiser Prado and Land Cruiser 200.
- 2. Lead generation
- 3. Market Evaluation
- 4. Mall and Corporate displays.
- 5. Researching of sales opportunities and possible leads to exceed sales goals and also to increase profit.

### > KOTTARAM TRADING COMPANY

SALES EXECUTIVE

**APRIL 2017 - OCTOBER 2017** 

### **Key Responsibilities:**

- 1. Sales of premium branded kitchenwares and crockeries under the brand name NOLTA Cookwares.
- 2. Monitoring customer buying trends, market conditions and competitor actions to adjust strategies and achieve sales goals.
- 3. Targeting new markets and increase sales through different techniques.
- 4. Maintaining of detailed records of sales progress, inventories and marketing success to better align goals with company priorities.
- 5. Execution of brand awareness programmes across the location.

### **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS**

- ❖ Master Of Business Administration Mar Athanasios College For Advanced Studies Thiruvalla 2015 -2017 (Standing Backlogs)
- ❖ Bachelor Of Commerce Parumala Mar Gregorios College, Valanjavattom, Thiruvalla 2012 – 2015
- Class of XIINampoothiry's College Thiruvalla2012
- Class of XSyrian Jacobite Public School2010

### LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCES

- **❖** Co-ordinator for the event YES CAN 2k15 Business Meet at KGA Crowne Plaza, Cochin.
- **❖** Hospitality manager for the event TANTRA 2k15 held at Mar Athanasios College For Advanced Studies Tiruvalla.
- ❖ Vice-Chairman for the event TANTRA 2k16 held at Mar Athanasios College For Advanced Studies Tiruvalla.

#### WORKSHOPS ATTENDED

- **Co-ordinator for the college "NAAC" accreditation process.**
- **❖** Participated for a three day "Outbound Experiential Learning" (OEL) programme by LEAP Learning academy, Coimbatore.
- **❖** Life skill training programme "Youth Empowerment Skills Plus"(YES+) by the Art of Living Foundation, Bangalore.

### PROJECTS COMPLETED

- **❖** Attended a one week programme "MACFAST Industry Interface" (MII) in Cochin.
  - **❖** A study on satisfaction among employees of TRAVANCORE CEMENTS LTD, Kottayam.
  - ❖ A study on the Brand Awareness among customers towards NOLTA products with special reference to Pathanamthitta district.
  - ❖ Organization study at OIL PALM INDIA PVT LTD, Kottayam.

### REFERENCE

Mr. Ajith Bhaskar

**Group Head Marketing** 

**Nippon Motor Corporation Pvt Ltd** 

Kalamassery Cochin Mob: 91 9847086008

## **DECLARATION**

I do hereby declare that the information furnished above is true to the best of my knowledge and belief. I hold myself responsible for the correctness of the content mentioned hereby.

Place: Thiruvalla

Date:

**ELDO VARGHESE PAUL**